newsofafrica.org 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy | News of Africa - Online African News - Daily Newspaper

This Privacy Policy describes the terms of my commitment to your privacy.

**PERSONS OR PARTIES COVERED**

This Privacy Policy is intended to cover all visitors to this website, all subscribersto lists or newsletters, all members, and all customers.  Persons who visit or view this website, whether intentionally or unintentionally, whether solicited or unsolicited, are described herein as “Visitors” and are parties to this Privacy Policy.  Subscribers to lists or Newsletters are referred to herein as “Subscribers” and are parties to the Privacy Policy.

**VISITOR,  SUBSCRIBER, MEMBER, OR CUSTOMER INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM ‘REGISTRATION’**

Registration means that the Visitor, Subscriber, Member or Customer takes active, positive steps to communicate information to this website.  This can include pages or ‘pop ups’ where you register for a newsletter or subscribe to a mailing list; it can include your participation in visitor surveys; it can include requesting information from the website via email.This information is kept at the highest level of security and is never divulged to anyone except for the purpose of communication with the visitor.

**INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM ELECTRONIC MEANS AND ‘COOKIES’**

Cookies can be used to electronically gather information about you.  Again, it may or may not be personal information, but it is information and by using this site you are expressly giving permission to use ‘cookies’ and to use the information gathered from their use to benefit you.  You also give permission to collect, archive, retrieve, and use any information collected for product design, product offers to you, and general commercial solicitation purposes by this site or joint venture partners, affiliates, and marketing organizations.

**SPAM**

By providing to this website information that forms the basis of communication with you, such as an email address, you waive all rights to file complaints concerning unsolicited email or spam from this website since, by providing such information, you agree to receive communication from us or other marketing organizations.  However, all email communication with you shall contain an ‘unsubscribe’ link where you may notify the website that you no longer wish to receive solicitations or information from the website and your name will be removed from the general solicitation database.

**DATA SECURITY**

This website takes measures to protect its data that contains information related to you.  However, as a consideration for viewing this site or interacting with this site in any manner, you waive all claims of any nature against this site concerning the loss, alteration, or misuse of information.  You must assume that it is possible for your personal data to be obtained by others, such as “hackers,” and used in an inappropriate manner that may cause you harm and that you agree that the site is not responsible for damages to you.

**DISPUTES**

As part of the consideration that the Website requires of the Visitor to view, use, or interact with this site, Visitor agrees to use binding arbitration for any claim, dispute, or controversy (“CLAIM”) of any kind (whether in contract, tort or otherwise) arising out of or relating to this purchase, this product, including solicitation issues, privacy issues, and terms of use issues.

In no case shall the Visitor have the right to go to court or have a jury trial.  Visitor will not have the right to engage in pre-trial discovery except as provided in the rules; you will not have the right to participate as a representative or member of any class of claimants pertaining to any claim subject to arbitration; the arbitrator’s decision will final and binding with limited rights of appeal.

The prevailing party shall be reimbursed by the other party for any and all costs associated with the dispute arbitration, including attorney fees, collection fees, investigation fees, travel expenses.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet. To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the  
following URL <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, TechTalkAfrica.com has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

**Collection of Personal Information**

When visiting TechTalkAfrica.com, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links to third party Websites**

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please don’t hesitate to contact us
